http://www.mensuas.com/pages/privacy-policy

Menu NEW ARRIVALSBEST SELLERS
UNDERWEAR
Back
UNDERWEARBikinisBoxerBriefsBoxer ShortsBriefsCostumesFlagG-StringTrunksThongsShapewearJockstraps
BY BRANDS
Back
BY BRANDS2xistAddictedAgacioCalvin KleinCover MaleDaddyDaniel AlexanderEdipousFeelGood DevilHonchoIntymenKyleMcKillopMensuasMiami JockObviouslyOtziPistol PeteSecret MaleView All Brands
BY STYLES
Back
BY STYLESCock RingsLace UnderwearFlagsExotic UnderwearEnhancing UnderwearCostumesMesh UnderwearSexy Underwear4-Way StretchPouch UnderwearLow Rise Underwear
SWIMWEAR
Back
SWIMWEARBikinisBriefsBoard ShortsSquarecutsTrunksBoxer
CLOSEOUTLogin / Register
Your Cart
No products in the cart.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our commitment to privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from our footer navigation that is found on every page of our website. When you register at Mensuas.com, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to process your orders, conduct account verification's, and to communicate with you about the status of your orders. We also use your email address to send you newsletters you are subscribed to during registration, as well as messages about Mensuas.com special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys. If you no longer want to receive the newsletters or other announcements simply unsubscribe by checking the unsubscribe links.
The information we collect This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Mensuas.com website. On some pages, you can order memberships, order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Billing address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/debit card information
Unique identifiers (such as username and password)
How we use information The primary use of your personal information, other than directly in connection with a purchase, is to efficiently provide you with personalized, relevant information.
We also use registration information to let you know about new features or other offers of interest from us and to address customer service needs and requests.
Cookies Contrary to the popular myth, cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computer's memory, but rather, record only information you volunteer to us upon registering or visiting the site. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you register at our Web site that enable our server to recognize or "remember" who you are each time you return. Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.
Log files Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
We use Google Analytics to track your website usage. The data collected is again anonymous so you need not worry on this front as well. This data is being collected just to analyze your usage and serve pages and offers which relevant to your buying needs.
Communications from Mensuas.com
Special offers and updates We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. We also send all registrants special offers and updates regarding our services. If you are a former customer, you will continue to receive special offers and updates regarding our services unless you choose to unsubscribe from such communications.
Newsletter If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our user's privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.
Service announcements On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional.
Customer service We communicate with users regularly to provide requested services and regarding issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, by the user's wishes.
Sharing—Third parties Mensuas.com will not disclose your personal information provided in connection with membership registration or purchases, except with your knowledge and consent as described in this Privacy Policy or as may be required by law or to protect the rights or property of Mensuas.com. We may share the information with our other websites namely.
Information submitted by you online (such as information about products you purchase from us, your name, address, email address) may be shared with companies with which we have a commercial relationship, including companies through which you reached Mensuas.com. For example, make a purchase with us because of a special offer made through another site acting as a distributor of our products, in that circumstance you will be considered their customer as well.
We will not, except as may be required by law, share with any other party your password or payment information. We may also share information about you (including name, email address, phone number, and postal address) to our marketing partners or other companies with whom we have a commercial relationship so they may contact you about information and services that we feel you would benefit from.
We also reserve the right to disclose aggregated user statistics, such as "45% of our users are female" to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties. Under the protection of confidentiality agreements, Mensuas.com may match common user information, such as name, address and phone number with third party data to avoid duplication and prevent errors.
Our commitment to data security Mensuas.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and other similar browsers becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just "surfing."
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment.
Mensuas.com reserves the right to make any amendments, modifications or changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If any material change is made to this Privacy Policy, we will notify our users about those changes via email. If you do not agree to such changes, you can modify your notification settings to opt-out of certain notices from Mensuas.com or its marketing partners. If users have any questions about the security at our website, users can send an email to Info@Mensuas.com.
How you can access or correct your information You can access your personally identifiable information collected by Mensuas.com by logging into your account and visiting the "Account" section of the website. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows an error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How to contact us Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at Info@Mensuas.com.
WHAT'S YOUR EMAIL?
ADD TO WISHLIST
Product has been added to your wishlist.
You can view your wishlist by creating or login account.
Please create account through ##customer_email## email
Login
Register
0
